登場
Lulu!!!
You don't have to be, like, sad. I mean, you'll get to join her after I exclude you, too.
from the beginning we hated you but also we loved you from the beginning as well
all we wanted was to become true friends with you so we had to cross the wall
ginko curry pie thank you lulu loves you she loves both of you so much
attention ladies above all things we must remain way invisible the time has come to begin the
exclusion ceremony friends are like more important than anything else agreed the friends gathered here
right now are us we are us those who like dare to contradict our feelings are a disgrace like
totally as are those who want to like way stick out from our crowd the ones that like refuse to
fit in with us are nothing but a nuisance people like that those who like don't follow social cues
are way evil humans and bears have been like way severed yet still certain people are like trying
to cross that wall we're here to decide who that next evil will be so we can like way exclude them
let's like search evil
select we have our evil so is everyone like totally ready all right we will now like totally exclude the evil
nega kuma energy replenishing and ready
both both nasty nasty nasty
nasty nasty nasty nasty nasty nasty nasty nasty
shoot her with that and she gets way blown to bits the bear will be extinct in like no time flat
hold on i'm the evil isn't that right all you really have to do is exclude me
of course that's exactly what we plan to do
this will be your punishment you're gonna get to kill your friends so we don't have to
you don't follow this world's rules so you're like way evil
we all stay invisible because we don't want to be anything like you
but if you're invisible how are you ever going to be found
my friend
you have to be kidding growl growl don't be ridiculous that girl is hardly a friend of mine
i came here to eat kureha subaki from the beginning that's all i wanted kureha is my prey nothing more
i've never once thought of that girl as my friend
ginko
she's not my friend kureha subaki is not my friend
that's a lie i know you're lying ginko
if you're telling the truth then why did you cross the wall and come over here
because i wanted to eat you growl growl and if that's true why did you stay by my side
why save me you both did what you could to protect me from the invisible storm
that's because if you had become invisible you wouldn't have tasted as good growl growl
you can stop this now ginko from the very beginning you were my true friend
you crossed the wall and you found me you saved me from the invisible storm and gave me love
you're wrong look i am only your enemy all i wanted was to eat you
get it now i'm a bear that bear has revealed her true form to us like explode that thing
oh yes i remember everything now
please stop it we have to exclude all traitors
growl
i don't understand does she not get to be approved because she's a bear
but why is being a bear bad if if she were a human girl would we be able to be together forever
would i be able to protect ginko please lady kumaria tell me
yes i'm the one who hoped for a promise kiss this is my fault
kareha subaki this is a challenge from the wall of severance is your love the real thing
yes absolutely if they grant a bear yuri approval in court she can become a girl
but to do that you have to let go of something it's usually whatever you care about the most
what does that mean well and this is just lulu's theory but lulu bets in ginko's trial when they
made her let go of something she had to let go of your love sorry lulu you were wrong
ginko didn't choose to let go of her love in order to get a wish
it wasn't her
it was me let the yuri trial begin defendant human kareha subaki is there anything you would like to
say i want to be with ginko forever please so i was hoping that maybe you could make ginko a human
girl like me your honor the defendant has obviously just committed the crime of pride
therefore the court must find her guilty crime of pride what does that mean basically it's about
you wanting to transform ginko yurishiro from a bear into a human but i have to change her because
because bears all get excluded and i know ginko will be much happier as a human anyway
whoa someone's confident sparkle sparkle and that is exactly what we're telling you is pride
well i don't care if it's pride or a crime please i want you to make ginko a human girl
very well however there is one condition what's that in order for your wish to come true you must
relinquish love you know what that means without love you'll forget all about your precious friend
ginko when you wake up understand that you will most likely reject her reject ginko
that day i made a wish that no one should ever make
i was foolish enough to believe my selfish love was actually the real thing
you must wait one day the time will come
when the invisible storm arrives you will find ginko yurishiro again
if you can make friends with her once more you must then exchange promise kisses
after that you can be together forever
sparkle sparkle
really
and now defendant human kareha subaki i ask you this will you choose to make ginko yurishiro a
human girl like you or will you choose to give up on love
sir i refuse to ever give up on love so please make ginko a human girl
lulu i hate to admit it but i'm afraid i wished for ginko to be human
and i did it in exchange for what was most precious
let the yuri trial begin
defendant human kareha subaki are you ready to admit your crime
yes i am i admit that i have previously committed the crime of pride
i did so by asking you to turn ginko into a human girl
now let me ask when you searched the invisible storm did you find what you wanted to find
what you hoped to find
yes
i met a girl there
she taught me so much
she found me
i found what i wanted
i found true love with sumika
sumika
i'm not afraid anymore
as long as i don't forget love i'll never ever be alone
if i don't give up on love even if i lose something i'll never be invisible
so i'm free now and i will leap into the storm
what does that mean
lulu
thank you
i'll take this star
this true love
and deliver it to ginko
stay away
face it ginko you are my friend
no you're wrong you're no friend of mine
growl growl
i'm a people eating bear
ginko the lone wolf's mane
and i came here to eat you
stop
stay back
hurry up and shoot me
otherwise i'll eat all of you
i'm a criminal bear
growl growl
admit it
please korea
stay away
i can't do that
i finally found you
help me with my wish
lady kumaria
whoa
it's lady kumaria
oh how wonderful
she's regaining her form
indeed she hath returneth
which means we gets to go
for this is sexy
shabadon doom
this is so cool
spartos
Kureha Tsubaki, is your love the real thing? Is it true?
Absolutely!
I will smash it! I will smash my image!
Lady Kumaria, make my wish come true!
I want to be a bear!
Yuri, approve!
Oh!
What?
Ew!
Kurea, how could you?
Ginko, thank you for refusing to forget love.
And thank you for never ever giving up on it either.
It's for you.
My promised kiss.
Did you know?
You and me are going to be together forever now.
Together forever.
Grouf, grouf.
A CRUDE!
That's like... way unbelievable!
A human like became... a bear?
Uh, like... way... gross!
Nasty?
We can't do it!
Stop! No shooting!
Nasty!
Like, hey!
What do you like waiting for?
A thing's not... human anymore!
It's a bear!
It's evil!
Like, exclude them!
We have to exclude all evil!
Aim straight!
Don't think about it!
Fire!
We worked hard!
We worked together!
And we got the job done!
Congratulations!
Ladies, we successfully excluded the terrible evil that had been overrunning this school for far too long!
What's more?
We know we've been right and should remain invisible at all times!
Let's begin the exclusion ceremony!
Friends are more important than anything else!
Agreed!
We've got the job done!
We worked hard!
We worked together!
And we got the job done!
Congratulations!
Ladies, we successfully excluded the terrible evil that had been overrunning this school for far too long!
What's more, we know we've been right and should remain invisible at all times!
Let's begin the exclusion ceremony!
Friends are more important than anything else! Agreed?
The friends gathered here right now are us!
We are us!
Fire!
That's all!
So let's begin the
The ones who refuse to fit in with us are nothing but a nuisance.
People like that.
Those who don't follow social cues are evil.
Now, let us decide on the next evil to exclude.
Nasty.
I found you.
We'll be together forever!
Thanks, Sis Lulu! I love you!
I love you, too!
And so, no one knows where the girls have gone.
But that is as it should be.
In the end, it is with your own love that the world awakens and changes.
The world remainsrikud primo ensemble.
I will.
Look at the numbers we look at.
We're here to throw away as soon as possible next year.
We are all in half of the more beautiful things,
you're always helping to keep it.
But that is why I'm coming back.
How am I now to survive in Russia?
You're hiding!
специ歏 defensively forehand,
Thank you.